André Arakelyan

An expert in quantitative analysis, predictive modeling, and systematic trading based out of Luxembourg. After studying general management at a top 2 German private business school, Mr. Arakelyan worked in management consulting for CFOs of large corporations listed in Germany (DAX), consulted ultra-high-net-worth individuals on digital assets, and finally worked as a trader for a Swiss multi-family-office with \$3 billion in assets under management where he was responsible for introducing and managing the emerging asset class of Digital Assets for entrepreneurs, large families, foundations, and companies.

Experience

Research Analyst and Founder at Theta-Digital Luxembourg Sarl-s Investment Research

Capellen, Luxembourg

2019 - present

- Building institutional grade digital asset model portfolios for UHNWI clients and family offices
- · Performing quantitative empirical research on liquidity and scalability of digital asset portfolios

Junior Portfolio Manager at Corecam AG

Vienna, Austria

2018

Swiss Multi-Family Office (\$3bn AUM)

- Responsible for overseeing a 1000 BTC portfolio of Digital Assets at a leading investment advisor for entrepreneurs, large families, foundations, and companies in Europe and Asia
- Generated in-house market research and created custom valuation models

Management Consultant

Wiesbaden, Germany

Undisclosed Family Office (\$100mm AUM)

2017

2017

2016

· Consulted management of a family office client on portfolio integration of Digital Assets

Strategic Management Consulting at KPMG

Frankfurt, Germany

CFO & CIO Consulting for large corporations (DAX)

Digital Transformation, Blockchain

- Technology Roadmap
- Enterprise Architecture planning, governance, and development

Risk Analyst at SmartStone Capital

Frankfurt, Germany

2016

Student led investment club

Analysed different trading strategies with the view to improving the risk-return profile

Head of Research at EBS.Invest e.V.

Frankfurt, Germany

2015 - 2016

- Student led investment society (80 members)
- · Organized and held finance, investing, and trading workshops for fellow students
- Lead a team of 15 student analysts & traders to manage the fund's portfolio
- Charity campaign: donated all profits to support local social projects

Head of IT at James Consulting GmbH

Frankfurt, Germany

2015

- Student led consulting firm
- Organized a research project for a London based hedge fund (\$25bn AUM)
- Supervised a state-of-the-art internal IT system

Workshops
Deutsche Bank (Global Markets), Nomura (Investment Banking Division), PWC (Strategy&)

Frankfurt, Germany

2015 - 2016

Education

European Business School (EBS Universität für Wirtschaft und Recht)

Oestrich-Winkel, Germany

2017

Focus: Asset Management

Extracurriculars: TEDxEBS, EBS.Invest e.V., James Consulting GmbH

Undergraduate Studies in General Management, TOP 2 University in Germany

Max-Planck-Gymnasium

Trier, Germany

2014

German Abitur (Baccalaureate, science focus)

Focus: Mathematics, Politico-economic studies, Biology